>> Brian Holt: 因此，我希望您返回到 App.js 。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So,
I want you to go back to App.js.
>> Brian Holt: 删除 ThemeContext， cuz 我们不再使用上下文。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Delete ThemeContext,
cuz we're no longer gonna use context.
那就把那条线删除吧
So just go ahead and
delete that line there.
请在此处删除 ThemeContext 提供程序。
Delete the ThemeContext providers here.
>> Brian Holt: 将此处的主题从应用中删除。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And
delete the theme here out of App.
>> Brian Holt: 现在我们要做什么，您也可以删除该导入。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And now what we're gonna
do, you can delete that import as well.
> > Brian Holt: 在上面，我们会说进口
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Up here at the top,
we're gonna say import
来自 "reatt-redux"。
from 'react-redux'.
这是一个与我们的背景相似的反应组件，
This is a react component similar to
the provider that we had for the context,
将向整个应用程序提供 React Redux 商店。
that's going to provide the React Redux
store to the entire application.
在这里， >> Brian Holt: 我们要说，
So inside of here,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: We're going to say,
提供程序和商店 =。
provider and store =.
>> Brian Holt: 实际上，我们可以自动从 ./store 中导入。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And we can actually
auto import that from ./store.
> > Brian Holt: 好的，然后我们就用这个把整个应用包起来。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, and then we're
just gonna wrap the whole app with that.
>> Brian Holt: 现在， Redux 可用于整个应用程序。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And so now, Redux is
available to the entire application.
>> Brian Holt: 对不起。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Sorry.
>> Brian Holt: 到目前为止还好吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Good so far?
>> Brian Holt: 感觉良好地删除了一些代码。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Feels good
deleting a little bit of code.
我最喜欢做的就是删除代码
My favorite thing to do is to delete code.
>> Brian Holt: 我们将它添加到 SearchParams，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
let's go add it to SearchParams,
所以这里是 SearchParams
so SearchParams here.
所以在这里我们要进口
So up here, we're going to import
( 连接自) 反应 - redux。
(connect from) react-redux.
>> Brian Holt: 我们将替换上下文引用。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: We're gonna
replace the context references.
>> Brian Holt: 因此，我们可以除去此处的 useContext ，并且
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So we can get rid
of the useContext there, and
我们就能在那里摆脱他们
we can get rid of ThemeContext there.
> > Brian Holt: 在这里，它的位置和位置，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
here where it says location and,
> > Brian Holt: 是的，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Yeah,
上面说的地方我们会把它说给动物
where it says location,
we're gonna put this to say props.animal.
>> Brian Holt: 不，对不起， props.location，相反。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: No, sorry,
props.location, rather.
> > Brian Holt: 我们也会在这里做道具。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: We'll take
in props up here as well.
> > 布莱恩 - 霍尔特: 好的，好的，把那个扔了
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, oops, get rid that.
>> Brian Holt: 好的，然后在其他位置引用位置，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, and then anywhere
else that refers to location,
我们需要这个值 = props.location。
we needs this to be
value = props.location.
而非 onChange 调用 updateLocation，
And rather than onChange
calling updateLocation,
我们会说 props.updateLocation
we're gonna say props.updateLocation.
>> Brian Holt: 然后是指主题的任何位置，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And
then anywhere that refers to the theme,
>> Brian Holt: 不是值
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Rather than the value being
主题我们要把这个改为 props.theme，
theme here,
we're gonna change this to be props.theme,
这里的 setThemes 将成为 props.setTheme。
and these setThemes here
are gonna be props.setTheme.
>> 布莱恩 - 霍尔特: 好的，现在我们要写的代码是
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, so now we're gonna
have to go write the code that injects
为了让我们能做到这一点
this from Redux for
us to be able to do that.
>> Brian Holt: 在此，我们也要将其更改为 props.theme 。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And here, we have to
change this to props.theme as well.
好了下面我们要在这里写两个东西
Okay, so down here at the bottom,
we're gonna have to write two things here.
>> Brian Holt: 我要写的第一件事是地图状态
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: First thing I'm gonna
write is map state to prop, so
我们必须写一个名为 " 常量映射状态图" 的函数。
we have to write a function
called const mapStateToProps.
所以这会把雷德克斯的东西拉出来，把它交给组件。
So this is going to pull things out of
Redux, and hand it to the component.
所以我们要去拿主题和地点
So we're gonna grab the theme and
the location, and
我们将给出一个主题和位置的对象
we're going to give back
an object with theme and location.
>> Brian Holt: 好的，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, and
那我们就得去做地图分派器了
then we're also gonna have to
do a const mapDispatchToProps.
这就是抓取读取数据，所以我可以看到的东西。
So this is grabbing the read data,
so it's the things that I can read.
我想读读这个主题和位置
I wanna be able to read the theme and
the location.
在地图 DispatchedToProps 中我想更新它
And here in the mapDispatchedToProps
I wanna be able to update it, so
我想让 Redux 的行动告诉它自我更新
I wanna be able to send actions to
Redux for it to tell it update itself.
所以我就去拿个调度功能
So here,
I'm gonna just grab a dispatch function,
我要把这件物品还给我
and I'm going to give back here an object.
其中一个将被称为集合主题
So one of them is going
to be called set theme,
这才是我们所称的对吧
cuz that's what we called it, right?
> > Brian Holt: 这将是一个功能，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And
that's going to be a function that,
>> Brian Holt: 以主题和
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Takes in a theme and
它调用分派，使用我们创建的 changeTheme 功能。
it calls dispatch, with that
changeTheme function that we created.
因为这是操作创建者名称。
Because that's the action creator name.
我们将进入这个主题。
And we're going to pass in to that theme.
还有 updateLocation的同样的问题。
And then same thing here
with updateLocation.
我知道这些都是不同的事情，没有好的理由
I recognize that these are named different
things, and there is no good reason for
啊，那。
that, so.
>> Brian Holt: 在此处更新位置，将在该位置执行。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Update location here,
his is gonna take in the location.
它会调用 changeLocation。
It's gonna call changeLocation.
再一次，这就是在顶部自动进口的汽车。
And again,
that's been auto imported at the top.
我们要去一个地方去
And we're gonna pass
in a location to that.
>> Brian Holt: 在哪里搞砸了 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Where did that get so
messed up?
好的，调度，这是一个箭头功能。
Okay, dispatch, this is an arrow function.
>> Brian Holt: 再次， changeTheme 和 changeLocation。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So again,
changeTheme and changeLocation.
您将在顶部的 changeTheme 中看到
You'll see up here at
the top changeTheme and
此处已更新 changeLocation 。
changeLocation have been updated up here.
你可以把这个钩子排在第 10 行
And you can get rid of this
hook right there on line 10.
> > Brian Holt: 好了，现在，我们要用连接来说，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, now,
we're gonna use the connect to say,
在这里出口缺省的 SearchParams 我们会说连接
export default SearchParams right here,
we're gonna say connect,
>> Brian Holt: (mapStateToProps，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: (mapStateToProps,
mapDispatchToProps)。
mapDispatchToProps).
>> Brian Holt: 然后，此函数返回了函数，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And
then this returned the function so,
连接返回将在 SearchParams 上调用的函数。
connect returns a function that then
you're going to invoke on SearchParams.
> > Brian Holt: 这是一种奇怪的方法，对吧 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: It's kind of
an odd way of doing it, right?
它是一种函数，它返回一个函数，但这就是它们选择这样做的方式。
It's a function that returns a function,
but that's how they chose to do it.
其实他们选择这么做的真正原因是
Actually, the real reason they chose
to do it that way is because that's how
设计师的作品
decorator's work.
最终，您可以使用连接作为装饰符。
So eventually you'll be able
to use connect as a decorator.
如果你不知道设计师是什么
And if you don't know what a decorator is,
因为还有很长的时间要来了
that's okay right now because
there's still a long time coming.
>> Brian Holt: 好的，真是太好了。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, so that was a lot.
但现在，我们在 SearchParams ，我们正在读和写 Redux。
But now, we have in SearchParams,
we're reading and writing to Redux.
让我们来看看是否能真正达到这个运行状态。
So let's see if we can
actually get this running.
它应该现在就在运行我们会看到的
It should be running right now, we'll see.
我要做 npm 的竞选
I'll do npm run dev.
>> Brian Holt: 现在，如果我们转至 localhost1234。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And now,
if we go to localhost1234.
现在我有了这个，但是它还在读和写这个位置。
So now I have this, but it's still
reading and writing to this location.
但现在，这个位置不再存在于组件中。
But now, this location doesn't
live in the component anymore.
它生活在 Redux。
It lives in Redux.
>> Brian Holt: 与此主题相同，对吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Same with this theme,
right?
它是在阅读和书写，不再是背景，它是它的阅读和
It's reading and writing, not from context
anymore, which is what it was reading and
写入之前。
writing to before.
现在它是 Redux的读和写
Now, it's reading and writing from Redux.